<xml>
<speaker>
	<title>Rakesh Komuravelli</title>
	<data>There are C.Vs which impress and then there are C.Vs which inspire and then there are C.Vs which leaves the most inspirational of us dumbstruck looking at the man’s track record. Rakesh Komuravelli surely falls in the last category. After scoring a perfect ten at BITS, Rakesh moved on to repeat this feat in his MS at UIUC scoring a perfect GPA of 4 there. Currently, he is pursuing his Ph.D. at UIUC under Prof Sarita Adve. During his 2 year stint at Oracle, Rakesh won an innovation award and a special contribution award. He has four pending patents in his name along with 10 other publications. Rakesh is a 2012 Qualcomm Innovation Fellow, a one in eight $100,000 award given by Qualcomm Incorporated that supports his research to address various hardware challenges in heterogeneous architectures. Today he is going to talk about rethinking today’s hardware for safe Parallelism.
</data>
	<topic>Today's hardware for safe parallelism</topic>
	<title>Rizwan Hudda</title>
	<data>
	Rizwan Hudda graduated from the Pilani campus in 2010 with Bachelors in Computer Science and a special respect from half of the 06A7 batch for his help in building the 50% PLCC assignment. Rizwan is perhaps one of the few prolific BITSian programmers who toiled away many nights acing CodeChef and TopCoder challenges. He also deployed his skills building interesting projects with the Computer Science Association. Rizwan worked at DE Shaw for one year and is currently pursuing an MTech in CS at IIT Kanpur, where his research work focuses on Randomized Algorithms and Machine Learning. With his passion towards theory, he will be the perfect person to talk about Algorithms at ART. Apart from computers, Rizwan looks forward to having a chit-chat outside LTC about his love towards sitcoms and movies.
</data>
	<topic>Randomized Algorithms</topic>
	<title>Arpit Agarwal</title>
	<data>Before passing out in 2011, Arpit Agarwal had quite an industrious life back here in Pilani with one of his projects being chosen for the GE Innovation Award along with few other patent worthy projects. Arpit was always research oriented which is evident by the fact that he gave up his PS2 for a thesis at National University of Singapore following it with his Master’s at UIUC on Tele-immersive systems under Prof. Klara Nahrstedt. Apart from his work on Tele-immersive systems, for what might be a super-human feat for most of us, he out-performed his competitors at the Facebook Hackathon. Arpit is a 2013, Siebel Scholar awardee. This prestigious award is given to 85 students from the top most universities around the world. At ART, Arpit’s talk would mainly focus on the Tele-immersive systems and what goes into building end-to-end systems.
</data>
	<topic>Tele-immersive systems</topic>
	<title>Vishwa Parekh</title>
	<data>
	Last sighted in 2011 on the Pilani soil, Vishwa Parekh is currently pursuing his Masters from Johns Hopkins University. Coding is not his only forte; he has participated in national level swimming competitions also. When most of his class-mates were racking their brains to understand what Pilani is, Vishwa spent most of his time at Pilani understanding human brain. In addition to this, he developed devices that could assist the blind, paralyzed and other differently disabled people. During his time at Hopkins, he has worked on multiple interesting challenges like developing brain computer interfaces that enable humans to control robots directly via their brain, methodologies to improve cancer diagnosis, and surgical devices and robots that drive the modern day surgeries. At ART, he is going to talk about Integration of Computer Science and Medicine.
</data>
	<topic>Integration of Computer Science and Medicine</topic>
	<title>Rajat Tibrewal</title>
	<data>
	Rajat Tibrewal, endearingly referred to as Tibbu or Chacha-ji during his BITSian days graduated from Pilani in 2011 with a dual degree in Physics and Computer Science. Having worked in IBM research and INSEAD France as an intern, Rajat is currently working in Google on multiple back-end systems- developing critical infrastructure for Google Apps for Business. A member of the English press Club, ELAS and the APOGEE Co-ordinator for CSA, friends from those times remember Rajat as a stingy-nerd and a brilliant quizzer.In this edition of ART, Rajat will deliver a talk on what it means to run your DSA lab assignment at Google scale.
</data>
	<topic>What it means to run DSA lab assignment at Google Scale</topic>
	<title>Chinmay Kulkarni</title>
	<data>A 2009 BITS pass-out, Chinmay Kulkarni is currently pursuing his PhD at Stanford University focused on peer processes in Massive Open Online Learning. His work at Microsoft Research on projects to enable interactive storytelling introduced him to formal research in Human-Computer Interaction. Later, he also interned with Google to explore the field of Social Computing and apply the same to facilitate High Quality Education. At ART today he shall talk about how to leverage Computer Science to create tomorrow’s classrooms, workplaces and society. He would also serve to familiarize students with research opportunities that exist in the fields of Human-Computer Interaction and Social Computing. 
	</data>
	<topic>Human-Computer Interaction</topic>
</speaker>
</xml>